const content = {
  react: [
    {
      question: "Is React.js a framework?",
      answer: "true",
    },
    {
      question: "Functional conponent uses Hooks",
      answer: "true",
    },
    {
      question: "All lifecicle method are executed after component mounted",
      answer: "false",
    },
    {
      question: "Are props objects?",
      answer: "true",
    },
    {
      question: "Does React.js use realDOM?",
      answer: "false",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Do you get any errors if you create the components names start with a lowercase?",
      answer: "true",
    },
    {
      question: "Can we use React Hooks in Class components?",
      answer: "false",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Does componentDidMount() get executed after the fisrt rendering?",
      answer: "true",
    },
    {
      question: "The fragments let you add extra nodes to the DOM?",
      answer: "false",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Does the React component get re-rendered when you update the state without setState?",
      answer: "false",
    },
  ],
  js: [],
};

export default content;
